[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of this is the general name for the type of pasta shaped as swirls?", "correct_answer": "fusilli", "incorrect_answers": ["macaroni", "lasagne", "spaghetti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of alcohol is used for the preparation of the Bacardi cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Rum", "incorrect_answers": ["Vodka", "Gin", "Bourbon whiskey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many glasses of milk is recommended for people 50+ each day?", "correct_answer": "3-4", "incorrect_answers": ["2-3", "0-1", "1-2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rene Descartes, who is given credit for the invention of analytic geometry in 1637, may have been preceded in this regard by which French mathematician?", "correct_answer": "Fermat", "incorrect_answers": ["Fourier", "LaPLace", "LaGrange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This enormous mythical white bird, which appears in 8th-century Middle-Eastern books, is said to be able to lift and eat even elephants.", "correct_answer": "Roc", "incorrect_answers": ["Medusa", "Lordi", "Phoenix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress, nicknamed The Divine Sarah, supposedly slept in a coffin, claiming it helped her understand her tragic roles?", "correct_answer": "Sarah Bernhardt", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Brightman", "Sarah Silverman", "Sarah Paulson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of respiratory organs do lungfish have?", "correct_answer": "They have both lungs and gills.", "incorrect_answers": ["Lungfish do not have any respiratory organs. They absorb oxygen through their skin.", "They breathe only with gills.", "They do not have gills, they use their lungs for respiration."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that some football players fathers are lobbying to have Grant Taylor fired in Facing the Giants?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of creature is Durza, the powerful evil entity in Eragon?", "correct_answer": "A Shade", "incorrect_answers": ["A Demon", "A Spectre", "A Dark Sorcerer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Goonies, what does Andys boyfriend call her when she refuses to come up out of the well?", "correct_answer": "A Goonie", "incorrect_answers": ["A Trader", "A Slut", "A Brat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors of the three vertical stripes on the national flag of Spain?", "correct_answer": "Red, yellow, red", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue, white, blue", "Yellow, red and black", "White, blue and red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the family that gets Lost in Space in this 1998 sci-fi movie by the same name?", "correct_answer": "Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Carusoe", "Smith", "Peabody"]}]